pitara.com 2014-02-24

# Pitara Kids Network : Privacy Policy

|  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
---|---  
   |  |   
**Legal**  
---  
  
[ **Privacy Policy** ] [**Conditions of use** ]

**Privacy Policy**   
Pitara Kids Network Pvt. Limited knows and appreciates that information that you provide is sensitive. Almost all the content on this site is available without registration and without providing any information. However, we do seek some information for you, sometimes. Especially when we are running some campaign, or promotion. When ever we seek information we ensure that it is kept confidential and is used very carefully and sensibly. 

This document describes our privacy policy. By visiting the Pitara Network of sites you are accepting the practices described in this entire document. 

The information that we gather from customers helps us personalise and continually improve the quality of your experience with us. We give you some instances of the types of information that we gather: 

* **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our services. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customising future interaction for you, improving our services and communicating with you. 
* **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many other Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our network sites. 
* **E-mail Communications:** Whenever you write to us for some information or with some query. 
* **Information from Other Sources:** For reasons such as improving personalisation of our service (for example, providing better recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources or places (such as if you participated in some Pitara event) and add it to our database. 
**Does Pitara Share the Information It Receives?**   
Information about our customers is an important part of our business - we are not in the business of selling it to others. The information we receive or collect is used for enhancing the experience you have with us. We do not share customer information with anybody outside Pitara Kids Network Private Limited. And even within the organisation, it is shared with those who have a role in serving you better. Even when we send promotional offers to our select audience on behalf of other businesses, we do not give that business your name and address. Every communication that we send out carries remove instructions, and we respect your right to not receive any communications from us. 

**Under what cases or circumstances is the information shared?**

* **Legal Necessity:** We may choose to release accounts and other personal information when it is necessary for complying with law or in the interests of protecting the rights, property or safety of Pitara, our users, or others. 
* **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive adequate notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have the option of choosing not to share the information. 
* **For dispatch of prizes and awards:** From time to time we run sponsored contents and promotions, which have prizes associated with them. Often the prizes are dispatched by third party vendors or by the sponsors. For this purpose we may share the information with them.
**How Secure Is Information About You?**   
The credit card number you give while shopping on www.pitara.com/shopping/children.asp, does not come to us. All transactions are processed through Amazon.com's secure payment gateway, one of the world's most trusted online retailers.. It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish with your work on a shared computer. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**  
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such features as All About You, Wish List and Customer Reviews. You can add or update certain information on pages where you have earlier provided the information. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, you can remove yourself from the list by following instructions given at the bottom of all such mails. 

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use such important features as 1-Click and New for You if you do not use cookies. 

**Advertising**   
At this time we use Google as a third-party advertising company to serve ads on our website. They may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by them please visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Children**   
Pitara Kids Network Private Limited does not sell products to children under 18. We sell children's products to be purchased by adults. If you are under 18, you may use [www.pitara.com/shopping/children.asp](http://www.pitara.com/shopping/children.asp) only with the consent of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**   
If you choose to visit Pitara network of sites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of the law of the state of Haryana, India. If you have any concerns regarding our privacy policy, kindly respond to us at [info@pitara.com](mailto:info@pitara.com) and we shall try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change parallely and the use of the information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use.   
  
|  | 

|   
|  |  |
